const question = [
  {
    "question": "About how many computer languages are in use?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "5000",
      "2000",
      "500"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Q34 say the full meme dialogue?",
    "options": [
      "Pols agyee Pols",
      "Im Batman",
      "Tam to bade Heavy driver niklee",
      "Aaj gadi tera bhai chalaega"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is not an early computer?",
    "options": [
      "UNIVAC",
      "INIAC",
      "NASA",
      "SAGE"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Lagrange points are there in the solar system?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the current president of JLUG?",
    "options": [
      "Miss Ishita Modi Ma’am",
      "Mr. Klevin Pascal Sir",
      "Mr. Mustkeem Arsh Sir",
      "Mr. Saket Gupta Sir"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Avenger possesses the ability to manipulate time?",
    "options": [
      "Doctor Strange",
      "Scarlet Witch",
      "Vision",
      "Ant-Man"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the real name of the mutant known as Wolverine?",
    "options": [
      "Logan",
      "Erik",
      "Scott",
      "Charles"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "SAY THE FULL DIALOGUE !!!",
    "options": [
      "Ekdum se halat badal gye, jazbaat badal gye",
      "Peeche dekho, Peeche",
      "Kya hai Sachin me, Lappu sa Sachin hai",
      "bhaiya fas gye baman ki ladki ke chakkar me"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Guess the meme?",
    "options": [
      "Systummmm",
      "Badmosii",
      "Mai to tut gya bhaii",
      "Humpe to hai hi na"
    ],
    "correctOption": 3, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is not one of the early ways to use the internet?",
    "options": [
      "Gopher",
      "Telnet",
      "FTP",
      "Blogging"
    ],
    "correctOption": 3, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Guess the anime?",
    "options": [
      "Kirito",
      "Asuna",
      "Krillin",
      "Doraemon"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Which department building is the oldest in the college?",
    "options": [
      "Electrical department",
      "Maths department",
      "Chemistry department",
      "Civil department"
    ],
    "correctOption": 3, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
  "question": "Guess the anime?",
  "options": [
    "Dr. Stone",
    "Adventures of Luffy",
    "One Piece",
    "Attack on Titan"
  ],
  "correctOption": 2, // Index of the correct option (One Piece)
  "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Who coined the term 'Artificial intelligence'?",
      "options": [
        "DONALD ERVIN KNUTH",
        "CHARLES BACHMAN",
        "HERBERT A. SIMON",
        "JOHN MCCARTHY"
      ],
    "correctOption": 3, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "I am from the college but not a part of it. Who am I?",
    "options": [
      "Robertson Lake",
      "IP Department",
      "NCC department",
      "AI Department "
    ],
    "correctOption": 1, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of our alumni appeared in most popular comedy movies like ‘Phir Hera Pheri and Bhaagam bhaag‘?",
    "options": [
      "MR. Manoj Joshi",
      "MR. Ashutosh Rana",
      "MR. Sharat Saxena",
      "MR. SK Joshi"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "This line is from which popular movie ‘’dosti ka ek usool hai madam- no sorry, no thank you’’..",
    "options": [
      "Kuch Kuch Hota Hai",
      "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
      "Andaz Apna Apna",
      "Maine Pyaar Kiya"
    ],
    "correctOption": 3, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Jab We Met,' what is the name of Geet’s cousin?",
    "options": [
      "ROOP",
      "SIMRAN",
      "PREET",
      "PRIYA"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Who directed the 2008 superhero film 'The Dark Knight'?",
    "options": [
      "Christopher Nolan",
      "Zack Snyder",
      "Joss Whedon",
      "Tim Burton"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the real name of the superhero known as The Flash?",
    "options": [
      "Barry Allen",
      "Hal Jordan",
      "Arthur Curry",
      "Victor Stone"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
 
  {
    "question": "Who is this character?",
    "options": [
      "Gian if he was fit",
      "Kakashi",
      "Takeshi",
      "Suneo"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Batman's loyal butler and confidant?",
    "options": [
      "Alfred Pennyworth",
      "Harvey Dent",
      "Oswald Cobblepot",
      "Jonathan Crane"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "According to this song, what brand of perfume does Pappu wear?",
    "options": [
      "Prada",
      "Gucci",
      "Armani",
      "Chanel"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Guess the song name?",
    "options": [
      "SURAJ hua maddham, chaand jalne laga",
      "Khoya Khoya Chand, Khula Aasman",
      "Suraj Chachu sogye, Chanda Mama Jage",
      "Haye Garmi"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Guess the song?",
    "options": [
      "Tere liye dil ka telephone, bajta ring ring rara ring",
      "Tune mari entriyaan, dil me baji ghantiyaan",
      "Mai hu Gian",
      "Dil zambhal sa zara"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0, // Index of the correct option
    "points": 10
  }
];

module.exports = { question };
